<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Brand guidelines on ainsley.dev</title><link>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/</link><description>Recent content in Brand guidelines on ainsley.dev</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><copyright>ainsley.dev LTD is a registered company in England and Wales. Company Number 12478393. ©2022 ainsley.dev LTD. All rights reserved.</copyright><atom:link href="https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Logo</title><link>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/logo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/logo/</guid><description>Logo This is the ainsley.dev logo. It is our primary graphic device and should be the first choice when choosing a graphic element to represent the ainsley.dev brand. Please do not edit, change, distort, recolour or reconfigure the logo. Colours Our logo should always be all black, all white, or white symbol with black word mark and vice versa. It never takes on any additional colours, and cannot be placed on top of any colour within the ainsley.</description></item><item><title>The Ʌ symbol</title><link>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/a-symbol/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/a-symbol/</guid><description> The Ʌ symbol The Ʌ symbol can be used in a variety of ways to add movements and dynamism to a static presentation or document. Colours The symbol should either be in full colour (tangelo &amp; topaz) or should be an opaque black and white version as shown below. The grey version can be used at 30% opacity or 100%. Clearspace Appropriate spacing should be placed around the symbol.</description></item><item><title>Colour</title><link>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/colour/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/colour/</guid><description> Colour Whilst the brand doesn’t feature many colours the combinations below are sure to create striking and minimal combinations. Primary Secondary &amp; Text</description></item><item><title>Fonts</title><link>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/fonts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/fonts/</guid><description> Fonts The ainsley.dev brand has three typefaces. The primary serif font is Plus Jakarta Sans; wherever this is unavailable, the operating system font stack should be used. Plus Jakarta Sans
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz 1234567890(,.;:?!$&amp;*) Times New Roman
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz 1234567890(,.;:?!$&amp;*) Jetbrains Mono
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz 1234567890(,.;:?!$&amp;*)</description></item><item><title>Typography</title><link>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/typography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/typography/</guid><description>Typography The ainsley.dev brand has a rich library of typography, headings and captions to choose from that add dynamism and a rich feel. Headings H1
Heading 1 H2
Heading 2 H3
Heading 3 H4
Heading 4 H5
Heading 5 H6
Heading 6 Modifications Link
Link Italic
I’m baby umami pickled narwhal
Strikethrough
I’m baby umami pickled narwhal Small
Small Code
git status Body Lead
I’m baby umami pickled narwhal woke food truck tilde gastropub polaroid forage.</description></item><item><title>Iconography</title><link>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/iconography/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/iconography/</guid><description>Iconography The icons used for the ainsley.dev brand are shown below. They include one arrow that can be used at different angles and social share handles. Arrow
Social</description></item><item><title>Components</title><link>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/components/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/components/</guid><description>Components This selection of components makes up the ainsley.dev brand and are the building blocks of any material or site asset. Buttons Buttons should appear with an arrow next to them. If placed on a dark background, a white button should be used and visa versa. A button A button Tags Small tags are used for categorising content for blog posts and articles. As with buttons, they should be placed with the background colour in mind.</description></item><item><title>Media</title><link>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/media/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://staging.ainsley.dev/brand/media/</guid><description> Media Images and videos should be simple with no box shadow, no border radius and be kept to the original aspect ratio where possible. Imagery Video</description></item></channel></rss>