<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ainsley.dev</title>
    <link>https://ainsley.dev/</link>
    <description>Recent content on ainsley.dev</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <copyright>ainsley.dev LTD is a registered company in England and Wales. Company Number 12478393. ©2022 ainsley.dev LTD. All rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 10:48:28 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ainsley.dev/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Launching Dec’s Pets into the E-Commerce market</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/work/decspets/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/work/decspets/</guid>
      <description>Client Dec&amp;rsquo;s Pets is an online e-commerce marketplace which started operating in 2018. They are a family run business specialising in pet retail, catering for all manners of pet care. They provide a large variety of services to their main clientele, based in Ireland, but wanted to reach a wider audience.
Brief ainsley.dev was tasked to modernise the website using a fun and family friendly design, and to make the site more user-friendly for buying products with ease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Logo</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/brand/logo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/brand/logo/</guid>
      <description>Logo This is the ainsley.dev logo. It is our primary graphic device and should be the first choice when choosing a graphic element to represent the ainsley.dev brand. Please do not edit, change, distort, recolour or reconfigure the logo. Colours Our logo should always be all black, all white, or white symbol with black word mark and vice versa. It never takes on any additional colours, and cannot be placed on top of any colour within the ainsley.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ʌ symbol</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/brand/a-symbol/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/brand/a-symbol/</guid>
      <description>The Ʌ symbol The Ʌ symbol can be used in a variety of ways to add movements and dynamism to a static presentation or document. Colours The symbol should either be in full colour (tangelo &amp;amp; topaz) or should be an opaque black and white version as shown below. The grey version can be used at 30% opacity or 100%. Orientation The symbol can be placed directly in line with the background, as shown above, or be used off-centre with the tail of the symbol being placed at the cut-off point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colour</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/brand/colour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/brand/colour/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fonts</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/brand/fonts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/brand/fonts/</guid>
      <description> Fonts The ainsley.dev brand has three typefaces. The primary serif font is Plus Jakarta Sans; wherever this is unavailable, the operating system font stack should be used. Plus Jakarta Sans
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz 1234567890(,.;:?!$&amp;*) Times New Roman
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz 1234567890(,.;:?!$&amp;*) Jetbrains Mono
ABCDEFGHIJKLMNOPQRSTUVWXYZ abcdefghijklmnopqrstuvwxyz 1234567890(,.;:?!$&amp;*) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Typography</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/brand/typography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/brand/typography/</guid>
      <description>Typography The ainsley.dev brand has a rich library of typography, headings and captions to choose from that add dynamism and a rich feel.
Headings Heading 1 Heading 2 Heading 3 Heading 4 Heading 5 Heading 6 I’m baby umami pickled narwhal woke food truck tilde gastropub polaroid forage. Chicharrones kickstarter hell of, narwhal craft beer XOXO literally gluten-free. ruffaut hella live-edge squid, ramps pickled dreamcatcher.
Bold Italic Strike
foo bar func main() { fmt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Iconography</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/brand/iconography/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/brand/iconography/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Components</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/brand/components/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/brand/components/</guid>
      <description> Components This selection of components makes up the ainsley.dev brand and are the building blocks of any material or site asset.
{{ .File }}hhh </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Media</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/brand/media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/brand/media/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing something blah blah</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/work/royal-beauty/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 10:48:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/work/royal-beauty/</guid>
      <description>Client Katherine at Royal Beauty specialises in a wide selection of massages and beauty treatments, helping clients to de-stress and unwind. They pride themselves on creating a warm and friendly atmosphere, where clients can let go of their stress, enjoy a relaxing massage experience and leave feeling refreshed and revitalised.
Link https://katherinebodycare.co.uk Strategy Website branding Landing page UI/UX Technologies Flat HTML, CSS &amp;amp; JS Contact form (PHP) AOS Brief With no existing website, Katherine at Royal Beauty obtained all of their traffic via Treatwell .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doing something blah blah</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/work/scotts-guttering/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 10:48:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/work/scotts-guttering/</guid>
      <description>Client Established in 2019, Scott&amp;rsquo;s Guttering specialises in gutter clearance and repairing leaking or broken gutters in the South East, across 2 &amp;amp; 3 storey residential and commercial properties. They also provide fascia, sofitt and conservatory washes, and bird pest control solutions.
Link https://scottsguttering.co.uk Strategy Website branding Landing page UI/UX Technologies Flat HTML, CSS &amp;amp; JS Contact form (PHP) AOS Brief Scott&amp;rsquo;s Guttering wanted to bring a fresh, high-quality approach to the new website and attract as many potential customers as possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Driving more than 92% traffic to Oak Tuition</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/work/oaktuition/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 10:48:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/work/oaktuition/</guid>
      <description>Client Oak Tuition is a tutoring school established in 2017. Their tutors are highly qualified and have experience teaching in local schools. Their hands-on mixed method tutoring and knowledge of the National Curriculum and exam board requirements enable students to make visible progress and gain confidence.
Link https://oaktuition.ainsleyclark.xyz Strategy Full brand UI/UX Multi page site Technologies WordPress GSAP SVG masking Brief Oak Tuition&amp;rsquo;s previous website was a static build, created using GoDaddy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making Thinkopedia stand out from the crowd</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/work/thinkopedia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 10:48:28 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/work/thinkopedia/</guid>
      <description>Client Cody Dumbarton is a psychology graduate specialising in helping others enjoy their right to a healthy mind. Thinkopedia was created in 2019 as a non-profit organisation providing action-orientated guidance for those struggling with their mental health and to empower people as they begin to re-write their story.
Link https://thinkopedia.ainsleyclark.xyz Strategy Full brand UI/UX Multi page site Technologies Laravel barba.js Locomotive Scroll Custom Medium client Brief Thinkopedia wanted a minimalist, easy to use and interactive blogging platform.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Responsibilities as a developer for optimised SEO.</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/posts/optimise-seo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/posts/optimise-seo/</guid>
      <description>https://docs.google.com/presentation/d/1v5J1GJO6irV_4yhU9GF6r847EREBST0sLRz4nnUOsQ0/edit#slide=id.gb566807306_0_60 Go to one of your websites you have developed and turn JavaScript off, does the page still function as it should? Is all the content rendered? Do images and layouts appear correctly on the page? If the answer is no, it may be time to consider refactoring your code base to allow for a more SEO friendly website. As developers, it may be easier to use a particular framework or library or even add functionality via JavaScript, but consider the technical debt before you do.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From bedroom to agency</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/posts/bedroom-agency/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/posts/bedroom-agency/</guid>
      <description>Insert Lead paragraph here.
Getting your first development job is hard – really hard. Job offers usually require at least one year of experience for a junior position, there are tons of different languages to choose from, hundreds of boot camps, and thousands of articles and tutorials to read. All of this can be daunting when you&amp;rsquo;re first starting out.
So where do you start? In this blog post we&amp;rsquo;ll cover CV writing, portfolio building and tech busting to help you land that first dream job.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are GoLang interfaces?</title>
      <link>https://ainsley.dev/posts/golang-interfaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ainsley.dev/posts/golang-interfaces/</guid>
      <description>https://medium.com/rungo/interfaces-in-go-ab1601159b3a https://go.dev/doc/effective_go#interfaces https://go.dev/tour/methods/10 https://go.dev/tour/methods/9 Interfaces are a tricky subject to grasp in GoLang, let&amp;rsquo;s demystify when and how they should be used.
Interfaces are a difficult subject to grasp in GoLang, a lot of people find understanding what an interface In Go, is, and when and how they should be used effectively. They can however, be extremely powerful when used correctly and aid with unit testing your code.
What&amp;rsquo;s polymorphism? Put simply, polymorphism in programming means many types can perform the same tasks (functions).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
